hello everyone i hope you're having a
nice week and you are taking care of
yourself i just wanted to stop in and
give a very short little note
saying a huge thank you for the really
kind response in my last video
unfortunately i do not have a video this
week
because i um i started feeling very
poorly several days ago and
i just couldn't do my normal daily
activities and i didn't know what was
going on
thankfully i was able to get to a
hospital about an hour so away
and they were able to help me
and
i'm on some antibiotics i am already
starting to feel better and i will no
doubt be back to my normal routine by
next week but i did realize i definitely
had to take some time
to
recover a bit as i was quite tired and
nauseous from the antibiotics that all
being said
i have had a little bit of time off from
work and i have been doing a little bit
of painting
i have been reading a book
shady hollow
i
was really enjoying it it's a sort of um
murder mystery but at the same time it's
set in this really adorable cozy little
woodland grove full of sweet little
animals so it's quite funny to read and
i've definitely enjoyed something very
simple and escapist during this time
that i've been in bed quite a bit also
been lighting a lot of candles
because i always like candles especially
when i'm not feeling super well and i'm
reading a lot of books
so
no doubt i will be back to normal by
next week i need to be on these
medications for a couple weeks
but
i am hopeful that by next week already
be a lot better i really do wish i could
make a video this week but i'm just not
quite there so working with my camera
takes quite a bit of time and energy so
i definitely wanted to respect my um
my body and my need to
take it a little bit easier this week
please take care of yourselves eat good
food drink a lot of water sleep well
you know you're
your health is very important you know
whatever is healthy to you
internal external health mental health
spiritual health
all of that is quite important so
i will see you all next week and i'm
sending you all my love goodbye